Praise be to God. We praise Him, seek His help, and ask for His forgiveness.
We seek refuge in God from the evil of our souls and from our bad deeds.
Whomsoever God guides, none can misguide, and whomsoever He misguides, none can guide.
I bear witness that there is no god but God alone, with no partner.
And I bear witness that Muhammad is His servant and Messenger.
O you who believe, fear God as He should be feared,
and do not die except in a state of Islam.
O you who believe, fear your Lord who created you from a single soul,
and created from it its mate, and spread from them many men and women.
Fear God and speak words of truth.
He will correct your deeds and forgive your sins.
Whoever obeys God and His Messenger has achieved a great success.